
A simple file sharing and reading application used by myself everyday and want to share with you now.

Feature list:
○ File share: upload and download files between your iPhone/iPod touch and desktop.
○ File reading: supported book format: txt, pdf, image and web page.
○ File management: folder/file create, delete,edit,move.
○ File lock: lock individual file or folder and all files and folders share one password.